https://diveshows.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policyadmin2019-06-08T08:39:53+00:00
PRIVACY POLICY
The Dive Show Ltd is committed to respecting the privacy of its users. However, we do collect and use various bits of information about you through your use of this website, and this policy sets out the basis on which your personal data will be collected, stored and processed. The data collector for this website is The Dive Show Ltd, with its registered office, Suite B, 74 Oldfield Road, Hampton, Middlesex TW12 2HR, UK. Please note that this policy only addresses our activities, and other sites to which this website links may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.
1. Collection
We shall ask you to supply personal information (data) to us in the following circumstances:
(a) when you wish to buy or utilise any of our products or services.
2. Information
The personal data that we shall ask you to supply could include the following:
(a) your name, address, and email address; and
(b) your postcode and telephone number; and
(c) (if you make purchases) your credit card or other financial or payment details.
We may also ask you to provide other personal data to us for particular purposes, such as supplying our products or services to you. In each case it will be your decision as to whether you supply us with the information in question or not.
3. Use of your personal information
We shall only use your personal data for the following purposes where applicable:
(a) to send you emails regarding diving news and offers
(b) to provide you with products and services (which may include products and services that we supply in association with other businesses);
(c) to process any applicable payments from you;
(d) to send you information regarding our products and services with your consent;
(e) to send you information regarding the products and services of other businesses with your consent;
(f) to notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions from time to time;
(g) for our own internal purposes in connection with risk control, resolving consumer disputes; and
(h) for producing statistics and other information relating to our business and the users of our website.
WE WILL NEVER SELL YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS TO A THIRD PARTY or sell lists of emails to other companies.
We do however send emails from j2 Global Canada, Inc. our professional email provider. The emails will always provide value to the reader and the frequency is never more than two a week.
Persons who do not wish to receive e-mail messages can opt out by clicking on the opt out link. Or you can contact us at data@divermag.co.uk . The Dive Show supports the customer’s right to opt out.
General Information
Any information or statistics relating to our business that we disclose to others shall not identify you personally. We may, for example, perform statistical analyses of the behaviour of the users of our website in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site and to tell advertisers how many users of our website have seen or “clicked” their advertising banners. This information, and any other general information about our users that we share with advertisers and other partners, will not disclose personal information about you.
4. Disclosure of your personal information
We shall only disclose your personal data to other people in the following circumstances:
(a) to verify and process any payment instructions that you give us when you order any of our products or services;
(b) to other businesses, when we are providing products or services to you in association with those businesses (see 3(b) above);
(c) to prepare or send any communications to you, or to assist us in connection with any of our administrative or business functions, or in the provision of any of our products or our services to you;
(d) to verify your credit worthiness or financial circumstances, for the purpose of making credit decisions, and in connection with fraud prevention and tracing debtors; and
(e) if we are asked to do by any legal or regulatory authority, or if we believe that it would be proper to do so in connection with any legal or regulatory matter.
Unless they are already legally bound to keep your personal data confidential, we shall enter into agreements with anyone to whom we disclose your personal data under (a), (b), (c) and (d) above obliging them to keep your personal data confidential.
5. Sale and supply
We shall comply with the following restrictions in relation to your personal information.
(a) We shall not sell your personal data to anyone else.
(b) Subject to the exception in point 4(e) above, we shall not supply your personal data to anyone else so that they can use it for their own purposes. The only time your email address could be transferred to another party is if that party actually bought The Dive Show brand in its entirety. This would constitute the third party actually becoming The Dive Show.
6. Security of your personal information
We shall take steps to ensure that your personal data is kept secure whilst it is in our possession, and your credit card details will only be stored and transmitted by us in an encrypted form.
7. Other information that we collect
When you visit our site we may log IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes.
We may collect information about your viewing habits when you visit our website through your IP address and by using cookies and other web tools in the following ways.
(a) Cookies. A “cookie” is a small electronic file that collects information when someone visits a website. A cookie can identify the pages that are being viewed, and this can assist us to select the pages that the viewer sees. Some cookies only exist whilst viewers are online, but “persistent” cookies – which are not session-based – remain on the viewer’s computer, so that he or she can be recognised as a previous visitor when he or she next visits our website. This information allows us to collect information about a viewer’s browsing habits, and this can be useful in assisting us to monitor and improve our services. We do not store sensitive information such as account numbers or passwords in “persistent” cookies, and cookies, in themselves, do not contain enough information to identify you. You will only acquire a personal identity in relation to your browsing habits after you have formally provide us with your personal data for the purposes outlined in point 3 above.
(b) GIF and other web tools. In addition to using cookies, we might also use GIFs and other web tools to collect information about your browsing activities. In this respect the information that is provided is similar to the information supplied by cookies, and we use it for the same purposes. Information that we automatically collect and analyse about you may include: the Internet Protocol (IP) address that you use to connect your computer to the Internet; your login, email address, and password; the computer and connection information relating to you (such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform); your purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from this website (including date and time); and any items you viewed or searched for. Any information that we acquire about you using cookies, GIFs or other web tools, or which we collect in any other way is subject to the same restrictions and conditions as any of the more formal personal data we collect about you.
NOTE. Some of the advertisements on our website may contain cookies, GIFs, or other web tools that are set by other people such as advertising agencies, or the businesses to which the advertisements in question relate. We do not have access to any information that might be collected in this way, and (if you are concerned) you should contact the advertiser for more information.
8. Amendments, cancellation, and contact us
At your request we shall make any amendments that you stipulate to the personal data that you have supplied us with. If you require it, we shall also remove your name and personal data from our database. This shall be on the basis that you shall be deemed to have cancelled any contract or licence you may have had with us that the personal data in question related to, and (as we shall not have been at fault in those circumstances) you shall not be entitled to any compensation or refunds in relation to the cancellation of the applicable contract or licence.
Please contact us at data@divermag.co.uk in relation to the matters to which this point 8 relates, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy.
The Dive Show Ltd is a company incorporated in England and Wales under Company Number 02602043.
Registered Office: Suite B, 74 Oldfield Road, Hampton, Middlesex TW12 2HR, UK.
days106hours03minutes15seconds36
Tweets by DIVESHOWS
Lily on the bright side
“For the past year my staff have been whispering to me that we […]
PADI ‘gives back’ with online gifts
PADI says it is “giving back this Christmas” by donating […]
DIVER TEST: Oceanic Veo 4.0 1460
The Oceanic Veo 4.0 is a very capable computer for advanced […]
About Us
Contact
Media
Advertise
Divernet
Subscribe To Diver
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Reject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
WordPress Image Lightbox Plugin
